[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "With a surface area of about 82,000 km\u00b2, this lake between Ontario and Minnesota is the largest single freshwater lake in the world.", "correct_answer": "Lake Superior", "incorrect_answers": ["Turkana", "Michigan", "Onega"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this game, played with 2 decks, you can make melds. Red and black threes have special significance and some cards are wild.", "correct_answer": "Canasta", "incorrect_answers": ["Rummy", "Russian Bank", "Gin Rummy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When is the expression seeing pink elephants most often used?", "correct_answer": "when people are drunk", "incorrect_answers": ["when you are dizzy", "when you see a ghost", "when going to sleep"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The atmosphere of Saturn consists mainly of what element?", "correct_answer": "Hydrogen", "incorrect_answers": ["Ozone", "Methane", "Helium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the Arabic phrase qahwat al-bunn, from which the English word coffee was derived through Turkish?", "correct_answer": "Wine of the bean", "incorrect_answers": ["Life in a bean", "Black wine", "Bean of the gods"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest living bird of prey on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Eurasian Black Vulture", "incorrect_answers": ["Philippine Eagle", "Booted Eagle", "Lappet-faced Vulture"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the colors on the national flag of Madagascar, adopted on October 14, 1958?", "correct_answer": "White, red and green", "incorrect_answers": ["Red, yellow and blue", "Yellow and green", "Blue, green and yellow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What unusual anatomical characteristic does the koala possess?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["The female has two vaginas.", "The female has two uteri.", "The make has a bifurcated penis."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Whose rulers wife dies giving birth to their son Theodred in Lord of the Rings?", "correct_answer": "Theodens", "incorrect_answers": ["Elronds", "Haldirs", "Denethors"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This construction in the United States is struck by lightning around 500 times a year.", "correct_answer": "Empire State Building", "incorrect_answers": ["Pentagon", "Statue of Liberty", "Golden Gate Bridge"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What part of a ducks body is recommended for treating coughs in traditional Chinese medicine?", "correct_answer": "Gizzard", "incorrect_answers": ["Eyes", "Bill", "Liver"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All dinosaurs died out due to a meteor hitting the Earth.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]